OHHHHH MY GOD!
I played I dropped me 24 7
What the fuck
I got all that
I saw you one day on God me that's the only day I saw you on God's computer
Yeah I was playing with Jeff because he was like
I'm so bad dude I can't I barely even aim
Oh my god I got high pain because the server location is Virginia what a freak
Bro I have 300 pain don't complain
I mean you don't live on Virginia from
You live far away from there
Yeah I always have like 300 pain
I never have under 100 pain
What the heck
Dude I suck I let you suck
They like Fortnite kids who are like
I have 60 pain this game is trash
I don't
I used to play Fortnite I used to do that same thing that you just said
Right it's 60 pain it's not that bad
Bro for like 30 FPS kids bro it is bad like it's the worst in the world
I have a 40 FPS
There's an FPS thingy the connect okay and shout out
You can actually get like a high FPS with no like already
Look I play on full screen and I still get quite a lot of FPS while recording
I push like PC to the limits
Bro when I okay so when I'm shooting right
So if I don't break what I do get more than 60 FPS
When I'm moving my camera right it moves fast like when I'm moving my camera it moves fast
But when I'm like now I'm moving my camera and I'm shooting someone it moves so freaking fast
And now I'm freaking so laggy bro I have 9 FPS so now I have 7 FPS
How can you play cool of duty how can you play cool of duty I not play roadblocks
You're because we're makes me ag bro like I don't know what's wrong with roadblocks
But right now I'm getting like so bad optimized man
How could you play cool of duty I not play roadblocks
Bro this game is game is 7 FPS
Brian may never set things
How can I play with this game is game is freaking 7 FPS though
I can I believe in can I believe in can kill someone
Look at that bro I'm trying to eat bro if I had high FPS right there I could up film I swear to you I could up film
Look how freaking slow my shots are bro
It's a freaking Lego game and it's worse than shit
What the frick oh my god dude
I just wish I could play you for I mean roadblocks good you know what I mean
My brother has better better mobile than me and he's never lost on our signal
Are you are thanks are you five yes why are you like automatic
What do you mean automatic
Like this automatic mode right
What do you mean by that like in settings
What do you want to look settings
No it's Mario I have it on ship like I have it like on the on the lowest like I have it right there on the lowest and I'm still back in
I have it on the lowest too
But then my brother never gave me the phone so
I should say like
So you said you're gonna get a PC right I hope full I hope so sit on I'm gonna get a Chromebook
I probably buy my family looks probably but why a Chromebook like
I mean anything that anything that I can play Arsenal really good
Chromebook is gonna be worse than your phone I think I don't know it's not gonna be better
I've played on Chromebook before it's not it's not that bad it's not worse than my phone
It is okay doesn't really like that much it is you can play on Arsenal and that game
You just need like a mouse you just need a mouse that's all
Like a else I think
I
Don't know
If you want to play on high graphics or stuff you should get a new one or but different one
Is she that put my graphics out of Maddie can we put it out of Maddie? No that that makes it worse
I don't know dude because like I'm trying to make it bass but it's
I played I dropped me 24 7
What the fuck
I got all that
I saw you one day on God me that's the only day I saw you on God me
Yeah, I was playing with Jeff because he was like
I'm so bad dude I can't I barely even aim
Oh my god I got high pain because the server location is Virginia what a freak
Bro I have free how to play
Don't go play
Okay wait.
I am so latched.
This game's glitched.
Wait what?
Okay.
I'll need to re-draw in row blocks.
Okay wait.
I am so latched.
This game's glitched.
Wait what?
Okay.
I'll need to re-draw in row blocks.
A-B-C-D sound test.
Hello, hello.